Okay, so it finished and you can see it ended up creating three files. Now every time you run
this, it does something a bit different. That's one of the bizarre things about this. For you,
it might have only created one file, indexed.html. For me, it created three. And I can click on them
to look at them. This is one file. This is one file. This is presumably quite a long file. There
it is. And then this is another one, the style sheet. So three files have been created.
They're sitting here in the directory and you can see what it thought about and what
it did all the way over here. Okay, it's time to give it a try. So I can look in my file
system at this directory called instant and we'll see that it has created those three files.
And I can double click on index dot HTML to launch this website.
I double click on it and up comes this.
Arrow Keys to Move and Turn, space to shoot,
neon arena first person shooter,
let's give it a whirl, start match.
Whoa, oh, so I am now controlling,
oh and I can hit this thing, and oops,
that is clearly an I was kill.
I'm not much good at this, but wow,
we just have a first person shooter game that was created
out of nothing doing no work whatsoever. Now look, it's entirely possible that when you
ran your one, it didn't work and something went wrong and I'll show you, but then you can just go
back and tell your agent that something went wrong and it will fix it for you. But before we do
that, I do think that I should redeem myself by at least trying to win this.
And so that I can,
victory, there we go.
So that I can show that I have some dexterity.
So success, we have been victorious in this game.
And it's pretty cool that it just worked like that.
It created these files,
it coded this game from just that simple prompt.
But let's see if we can make it a little bit better.
So maybe something didn't work, maybe the shooting didn't work, sometimes for me that
didn't happen once the keys didn't work at all.
I've tried this a bunch of times and it's a bit different every time.
But let's suppose we want the opponent to look a bit more awesome than just a sphere
like that.
So let's prompt here.
I'll say that's great. Please add some detail to the opponent so that it looks more like an enemy.
Let it be creative.
That is the instruction that we will give and we will see what comes of this.
It's now going to add some details and you'll see it editing and changing and I'll come back
in a second when it's ready for us to test it out again. Okay, well it tells us that
it's done that. So now let's go back, let's double click on index again, here we have
it. Oh, there indeed is a slightly more interesting enemy. And I, I, I won again. I'm
good at this game. It's an easy game. Okay, Well, let's go and do some more edits to the game.
All right. So back we go.
We'll say, please add a heads up display, H-U-D,
and also make the difficulty harder.
Let's see what it makes of this.
I'll let it do its planning next moves and it's thinking.
We will go through in more detail at some point about the planning and then executing
on these kinds of ideas and I will see you in a second when it's finished its work.
Okay, it claims again that it has done our bidding.
Let's see, let's bring up this.
Here we have it, start match.
Okay, it's... [laughs it's 30 seems more difficult.
All right, it achieved that goal.
Very nice.
So there you have it.
There you see a very unbusiness like example
of how quick and easy it is to have an LLM,
a language model, be our agent writing code with us.
It incursor, we had this conversation with the agent. It
created these three files that are now in instant and by iterating. By adding
some more comments, we were able to sort of work hand in hand at building this out
without writing a single line of code and it worked great. And if this didn't
work out for you, if it didn't work, then please do come back and iterate. And if you
get stuck and you're not able to get through some point,
then just delete the whole instant directory and start again,
create a new instant and give it a second shot.
Try different model options and try different ways to prompt it.
This is great experimenting.
This is not an important project.
This is just for you to get a first feel for it.
We will be doing so much of this in the next few weeks
until you are great at it. But now let me show you
one more thing.
Over the next three weeks, we're going to be using a number of different techniques
to get more and more sophisticated at working hand in hand with AI agents to build complicated
projects. And I decided to put some of those techniques to the test. I used a technique
called Ralph Loops with Claude Code to do this same project. And I did what people sometimes call zero-shot,
which is I just set it off. I didn't give it any feedback. It was one iteration, one prompt
only in this thing called a Ralph Loop that we will cover. And this is the result of it.
Let me show you what it came up with now. Okay, I'm going to double click on index HTML. All right,
well, that looks cool. This is the entry entry screen I'll make this nice and big
so you can see it fully let's start again.
"Fights" it says check this out look at that gun look at that oh my goodness
oh haha try not to get too distracted by this look at his energy there we go
I won and you can see my health and my kills up at the top. And you can see the map on the bottom right.
Do you see that, that little display there?
It's absolutely amazing.
And there's a health over here.
I can go and get a health to recover quickly.
There we go.
So this, I will stop playing.
That's not the point of this.
This is just to give you that teaser,
that example of what it's like to go pro
with this toolset.
This is using Ralph Loops, something that we will cover
and it's using Cloud Code to build out a whole application
like this.
But again, the thing to bear in mind
is that this is something where I just typed in a prompt
and let it go.
I didn't give it any feedback.
And it came up with this, which I think is really cool.
This is something that you'll be able to do too
in just a matter of days.
All right, so that concludes the instant gratification.
I hope that you feel gratified.
That was a lot of fun.
From this point on, it's all business.
We'll be building commercial stuff and we're going to start by actually discussing what this course is all about.